Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conferences, Conventions and Meetings, Series 4
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 2, 1997-09-19; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 3, 1997-09-19; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 4, 1997-09-20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 5, 1997-09-20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 6, 1997-09-20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 7, 1997-09-20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 8, 1997-09-20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 9, 1997-09-20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 10, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 11, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 12, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 13, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 14, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 15, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 16, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference, Tape 1, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference, Tape 2, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference, Tape 3, 1997-09-20 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 1, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 2, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 3, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 4, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 5, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 1, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 2, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 3, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 4, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 5 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 1, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 11)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 2, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 12)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 3, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 4, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 14)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 5, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 2, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 16)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 3, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 17)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 4, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 5, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 19)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 1, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 20)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 2, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 21)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 3, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 22)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 4, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 23)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 3, Series 1
  - IBT 28th Convention Las Vegas "History of Fighting", 2011 (Box 3, Item 31)
  - 2009 Teamsters Women's Conference (Box 3, Item 49)
  - Teamsters National Black Caucus 28th Annual Educational Conference and Banquet "Embrace Our History To Empower Our Future" (Box 4, Item 4)
  - Teamsters: Moving Forward Together 27th Convention Videos, 2006 (Box 3, Item 43)
  - "Teamster Women on the Move," Edited Master, BETA cassette, August, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "Teamster Women on the Move," Protection Master, BETA cassette, August, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "Teamster Women," Tape 1, BETA Cassette, March 4, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Teamster Women," Tape 2, BETA cassette, March 4, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Teamster Women," Tape 3, BETA cassette, March 4, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - "Teamster Women," Tape 4, BETA cassette, March 4, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Teamster Women," Tape 5, BETA cassette, March 4, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - "Teamster Women," Tape 6, BETA cassette, March 4, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 2004 Teamster Unity Conference, Las Vegas, NV, Dick Gephardt, Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 26th international Convention, June 25-29,2001; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 10, 1997-09-21; DVD (Box 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 11, DVD (Box 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 12, 1997-09-21; DVD (Box 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 13, 1997-09-21; DVD (Box 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 14, 1997-09-21; DVD (Box 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 15, 1997-09-21; DVD (Box 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 16, 1997-09-21; DVD (Box 1)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #1 Part 1 CDL, Overview, Series 4; VHS (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #2- Vehicle Inspection, Party 2A, Series 4; VHS (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #3, operating Techniques, Part 2B, Series 4; VHS (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #4- Operating Techniques, Part 2C, Series 4; VHS (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #5- Vehicle Safety, Part 2D, Series 4; VHS (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #6- Transporting Cargo, Part 3, Series 4; VHS (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Conversation of Teamsters Tape #7- Transporting Passengers, Part 4, Series 4; VHS (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #8- Air Brakes, Parts 5, Series 4; VHS (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #9- Combination Vehicles, Part 6, Series 4; VHS (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters Tape #10- Hazardous Materials, Part 7, Series 4; VHS (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Conference Food Delivery, 1995-09-28; Series 4; VHS (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Conference Food Delivery, 1995-09-28; Series 4; VHS (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - IBT 2003 Compilation, Series 4; VHS (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "100 Year Locals" RT 9:42, 2003-09-06; Series 4; VHS (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial "Retirees Speeches", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "Retirees Speeches", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "Retirees Speeches", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "Retirees Speeches", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial "Retirees Speeches", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial "Lifetime Achievement Winners", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHs (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial "Lifetime Achievement Winners", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial "Lifetime Achievement Winners", 2003-11-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - IBT Centennial A Strong Legacy, A powerful Future, Rough Cut, 2003-08-23; Series 4; VHS (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - IBT 2003 Convention Speeches 100th Anniversary, Bill Clinton, Hilary Clinton, Dick Gephardt, 2003-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - IBT 2003 Convention Speeches 100th Anniversary, Bill Clinton, Hilary Clinton, Dick Gephardt, 2003-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - IBT 2003 Convention Speeches 100th Anniversary, Bill Clinton, Hilary Clinton, Dick Gephardt, 2003-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - IBT 2003 Convention Speeches 100th Anniversary, Bill Clinton, Hilary Clinton, Dick Gephardt, 200-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - IBT Centennial Celebration Video 1:39:00, Series 4; VHS (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - IBT Centennial Celebration Video, Series 4; VHS (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - IBT Centennial Celebration Gephardt Speech, Master Copy, 2003-09-03; Series 4; VHS (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - LIUNA Centennial Wormhole Music Video, Series 4; VHS (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - LIUNA Centennial Legacy Moments- 5 Episodes, Series 4; VHS (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - IBT 100th Yer (Centennial) Anniversary Compilation Master Copy 1:39:18, 2003-09-06; Series 4; VHS (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 8- Window Dub (undated), Series 4; VHS (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 9- Window Dub (undated), Series 4; VHS (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 10- Window Dub (undated), Series 4; VHS (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 11- Window Dub (undated), Series 4; VHS (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Civil Rights Conference Tape 13 Closing, 1995-09-17; Series 4; Betacam and DVD (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Civil Rights Conference Tape 14 Closing and Break-up, 1995-09-17; Series 4; Betacam and DVD (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights IBT Convention Protection Master Exhibit Booth Video, 1996; Series 4; VHS (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 1- Window Dub, 1997-09-19; Series 4; VHS (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 2- Window Dub, 1997-09-19; Series 4; VHS (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 3- Window Dub, 1997-09-19; Series 4; VHS (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 2- Window Dub, 1997-09-21; Series 4; VHS (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 3- Window Dub, 1997-09-21; Series 4; VHS (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 3- Window Dub, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 4- Window Dub, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 5- Window Dub, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 6- Window Dub, 1977-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 7- Window Dub, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #1 Ron Carey; Intro Remarks: Claude Brown, music, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #2, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #3, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #4, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #5, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #6, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #7, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #8, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #9, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #10, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #11, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #12 Delores Huerta, UFW Mary Mendez Apple Organizing Campaign, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #13, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #14, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #15, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference #16, 1997-09-20; Series 4; Betacam (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 12, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 14, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 15, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 16, 1997-09-20; Series 4; VHS (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Human Rights Conference Tape 1- Window Dub, 1997-09-30; Series 4; VHS (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 1, 1991-06-24; Series 4; VHS (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 3, 1991-06-24; Series 4; VHS (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 4, 1991-06-24; Series 4; VHS (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Monday Tape 5, 1991-06-24; Series 4; VHS (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 1, 1991-06-25; Series 4; VHS (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 2, 1991-06-25; Series 4; VHS (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 3, 1991-06-25; Series 4; VHS (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 4, 1991-06-25; Series 4; VHS (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Tuesday Tape 5, 1991-06-25; Series 4; VHS (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 1, 1991-06-26; Series 4; VHS (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 2, 1991-06-26; Series 4; VHS (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 3, 1991-06-26; Series 4; VHS (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 4, 1991-06-26; Series 4; VHS (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Wednesday Tape 5, 1991-06-26; Series 4; VHS (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 1, 1991-06-27; Series 4; VHS (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 2, 1991-06-27; Series 4; VHS (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 3, 1991-06-27; Series 4; VHS (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 4, 1991-09-27; Series 4; VHS (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Thursday Tape 5, 1991-06-27; Series 4; VHS (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 1, 1991-09-28; Series 4; VHS (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 2, 1991-09-28; Series 4; VHS (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 3, 1997-06-28; Series 4; VHS (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - IBT 1991 Convention Friday Tape 4, 1991-06-28; Series 4; VHS (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 1, 1994-03-04; Series 4; VHS (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 2, 1994-03-04; Series 4; VHS (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 3, 1994-03-04; Series 4; VHS (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 4, 1994-03-04; Series 4; VHS (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Chicago, IL Tape 4, 1994-03-04; Series 4; VHS (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference NYC Part 1, 1995-06-03; Series 4; VHS and DVD (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference NYC Part 2, 1995-06-03; Series 4; VHS and DVD (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Women's Conference Video, 2000-05; Series 4; VHS (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - IBT Women's Conference Video, 2000-05; Series 4; VHS (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - IBT Women's Conference Video, 2000-05; Series 4; VHS (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - IBT Women's Conference Video, 2000-05; Series 4; VHS (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - IBT Women's Conference Video, 2000-05; Series 4; VHS (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - International Women's and HRC Conference Wyndham, Baltimore Tape 1, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - International Women's and HRC Conference Wyndham, Baltimore Tape 2, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 2, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - International Women's and HRC Conference Wyndham, Baltimore Tape 3, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 3, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 4, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 5, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 6, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 7, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 1 of 2, 2003-03-07-2003-03-10; Series 4; VHS (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD Tape 2 of 2, 2003-03-07-2003-03-10; Series 4; VHS (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Women's Conference Baltimore, MD General Session, 2003-03-07; Series 4; VHS (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Women's Conference Highlights "For Content Only" Rough Cut, 2004-06-24; Series 4; VHS (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - IBT Women's Conference Highlights '05, 2006-05-16; Series 4; Betacam (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Women's Confence Phoenix, AZ (3 copies), 2006; Series 4; 3 DVDs (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Convention, 1986; Series 4; VHS (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 1, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 2, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 3, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 5, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Vice President Al Gore Address Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Vice President Al Gore Address Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Vice President Al Gore Address Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Endorse Gore Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 1, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 2, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Unity Las Vegas Burning Concepts PGM 3, 2000-09-18; Series 4; VHS (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters International Convention Canadian Unity Amendment (2001) Master Copy 25min, 2003-06-25; Series 4; VHS (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - 2003 IBT Unity Conference- "Changing to Grow" Bally's Hotel Las Vegas, NV Tape 1 of 2, Master Copy, 2003-05-12; Series 4; VHS (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - 2003 IBT Unity Conference- "Changing to Grow" Bally's Hotel Las Vegas, NV Tape 2 of 2, 2003-05-12; Series 4; VHS (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - 2003 IBT Unity Conference- "Changing to Grow" Day Two: Tape 2 of 2, 2003-05-12; Series 4; VHS (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - 2003 IBT Unity Conference- "Changing to Grow" Day Two Tape 2 of 2, 2003-05-12; Series 4; VHS (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - 2003 IBT Unity Conference- "Changing to Grow" Day Two Tape 2 of 2, 2003-05-12; Series 4; VHS (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - 2003 IBT Unity Conference- "Changing to Grow" Day Two Tape 2 of 2, 2003-05-12; Series 4; VHS (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV Tape 1, 2004; Series 4; VHS (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV Tape 1, 2004; Series 4; VHS (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV Tape 1, 2004; Series 4; VHS (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV Tape 1, 2004; Series 4; VHS (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV "Ten Years of Broken Promises", 2004; Series 4; VHS (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Las Vegas, NV "Ten Years of Broken Promises", 2004; Series 4; VHS (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - 2004 Unity Conference "Disaster Relief" 27th Convention, Series 4; VHS (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Unity Conference Compilation (DVDs, 9 copies), 2005; Series 4; DVD (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Unity Conference 4 General Presidents, Raynor, Wilhem, Stern, O'Sullivan Intros by Hoffa, 2005; Series 4; VHS (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Unity Conference 4 General Presidents, Raynor, Wilhem, Stern, O'Sullivan Intros by Hoffa, 2005; Series 4; VHS (Box 202, Folder 4)
- General Presidents and Other Leaders, Series 5
  - TV News Dave Beck, ND; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Dave Beck, Seattle Citizen, ND (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - James P. Hoffa Coverage in Squash Box (CNBC) and Glenn Beck (CNN), 2007 (Box 3, Item 47)
  - James P. Hoffa Accepts the George Washington University Presidents Medal, 2014 (Box 3, Item 37)
  - James P. Hoffa Inauguration IBT #1, 1999 (Box 3, Item 42)
  - James Hoffa Sr. Vancouver Joint Council 36, 1969 (Box 3, Item 40)
  - IBT Hoffa for Teamster President, 1996; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Hoffa Slate/Leedham Slate IBT Teamster Candidate Forum, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - ABC Interview with Mr. Hoffa (18 Minutes), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 24th Annual Labor Awards Honoring IBT General President James P. Hoffa, ND (Box 3, Item 39)
  - General President Hoffa at ICTU Bi-Annual Convention in Belfast, Ireland, 2005 (Box 3, Item 44)
  - Face the Nation with Dave Beck, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Trip to Italy - Dave Beck, ND (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Longines Chronoscope with Dave Beck, ND (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Election: Indiana Teamsters: Jimmy Hoffa (30 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Face the Nation Hoffa Interview (27 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - King-TV Dave Beck Interview, ND (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - "Balancing the Scales" The Chattanooga Trial of U.S. v. James R. Hoffa (65 minutes), 2008 (Box 3, Item 32)
  - Teamsters Reel 1: General President Hoffa's Presentation of National Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Motor Freight Agreement with Central States Supplements Part 1, 1964 (Box 3, Item 33)
  - Teamsters Reel 1: General President Hoffa's Presentation of the National Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Motor Freight Agreement with Central States Supplements Part 2, 1964 (Box 3, Item 34)
  - Dave Beck at the National Press Club, 1953 (Box 3, Item 35)
  - Teamsters "English Speech", 1966 (Box 1, Folder 41)